Nico Reed

538 Vine St · Kent, Ohio, 44240 (330) 730-5519 · nr830411@gmail.com

Web Developer with immense coding knowledge & experience paired with an unmarred ability to grasp new technologies & software implementation. With a diverse background in HVAC tech, Customer Service and certification from Case Western Reserve University in Full Stack technologies such as JavaScript, SQL, Node & React. Someone who is not afraid to do any meticulous dirty work, but is also comfortable in the spotlight where direct communication and personal consumer fulfillment is necessary. An analytical mindset has allowed me to flourish in this changing career path and will no-doubt grant me the ability to to accommodate any engineering team.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Waiter, Bricco, Kent, Ohio

September 2017 - Present

- Allow guests to feel welcome and comfortable
- Keeping composure and order in a fast-paced and high-stress environment
- Party service for Bridal Showers, Birthdays, Business events Wedding Showers, etc.
- Professional wine presentation & bottle service
- Expo'ing orders to be sent out to tables during dinner service
- Maintain cleanliness of self and restaurant

Commercial HVAC Technician, EFE Protective Services, Massillon, Ohio

June 2017 – November 2018

- Worked with team to install and replace restaurant Hoods, roof mounted A/C units for commercial stores
- Installation of armaflex copper pipe insulation
- Traveled to.job sites in Kentucky, West Virginia, all counties of Ohio working on chain restaurant & gas station HVAC units
- Top-to-bottom installation of return and supply ventilation units
- Using Mastic to seal HVAC duct
- Skid steer operation
- Cutting and creating duct by hand using angled shears,/sawzaw
- Installing new thermostats for businesses/jobs
- Working alongside union employees on job sites. Electricians/Carpenters/Painters
- Building walk-in fridge/freezer units and welding copper piping for said freezers
- Setting and stationing equipment for stores yet to-be-opened

Waiter, Burntwood Tavern, Cuyahoga Falls, Ohio

September 2015 - September 2017

EDUCATION

Case Western University May 2020

Full Stack Web Development Coding Bootcamp

Ohio University January 2012

Concentration: General Education, focus in Journalism

Honors/Activities: Student Senate

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- Javascript
- SQL Programming
- ReactJS
- Microsoft Clients
- HTML
- CSS

- HVAC unit installations
- Fine dining service
- J Query
- Mongo